<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://charapagos.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 14:57:57 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://charapagos.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic information on charapagos</title>
      <link>https://charapagos.github.io/basic-information-on-charapagos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 14:57:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charapagos.github.io/basic-information-on-charapagos/</guid>
      <description> About charapagos Charapagos is a system to produce Cinematic Communication that is a new type of online communication with making the best use of digital characters.
Demonstration You can try the demonstration of Cinematic Communication from the below URL. Please do not forget to include emotional key words like &amp;ldquo;Happy&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Sad&amp;rdquo; in your message. Digital characters will act according to the key words.
https://raw.githack.com/charapagos/interface/master/cp_demo_v2_1/cp_demo_v2_1.html
Menu  Cinematic Communication Charm of characters to empower messages Three aims Realization of your imaginary world That is where creators come in Make the best use of digital characters Make use of the most common technologies Overcome ecosystems Network structure Emotional Engine Make use of online storage Data storage location Multiply Filtering System Combination of filters Types of data to be registered on filters Distributing expression data for characters Sharing methods for how to direct characters Technical approaches Scheme of Pay Forward Trust Alliance scheme Relationships between users and character data The right of character data Social approach Now is the time when everybody can be a creator Connecting between creators and users Importance of fostering users Experience of admitting the value of creativity Carrier educational activities Independent Animation Festival UNESCO Salon Films Competition Teenage Walkers Project  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>